

CONTACT

+506-72848535



Liberia, Guanacaste, Costa Rica



rodrigovidal278@gmail.com



rodrigo-vidal-portafolio.netlify.app



github.com/vidal1101

SOCIAL MEDIA



@rodrigovidalc



@rodrigovidalc



@Rodrigo_Vidal_C

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript

Java

Python

Dart

Flutter

Bootstrap

SqlServer

Docker

Git-Github

PHP

RODRIGO VIDAL CANALES

Software Developer

Developer of mobile and web applications with knowledge in back-end and front-end, developed through own projects and with experience at the business level. I seek to develop my career, helping to contribute with my skills and learn from others through good communication to achieve final designs that meet the needs and preferences of clients.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web developer - Internship at Rolosa company

November 2021 - May 2022 (6 months) development of custom modules using drupal cms

Java programmer - Freelance

October 2020 a January 2021

spreadsheet control software, implemented Hibernate + JPA

Web programmer - Freelance

March 2019 a September 2019

Creation of a web system of point of sale and accounting, developed in python

EDUCATION

Diplomado en Ingeniería en Tecnologías de Información

Diploma in technology with knowledge in hadware and equipment software.

COURSES

UDEMY- FLUTTER

Development of mobile applications for ios and android.

REFERENCES

Andrey Quesada Méndez +506-87024823 aquesada@rolosa.com